

Personal details



Eduardo Salazar



e.salazar.v.252@gmail.com



+58 426 536 79 89



Caracas - Venezuela



linkedin.com/in/ eduardosalazar-3a92791bb

Skills

Visual Studio	••••	
SQL Server Manager IIS ••••		
Manager	••••	
Azure DevOps	••••	
Trello	••••	
ASP.NET Framework MVC	••••	
ASP.NET Core MVC	••••	
ASP.NET Blazor	••••	
HTML5/CSS/	••••	
JavaScript C#	••••	
SQL	••••	
Microsoft Office	••••	

Languages

Spanish	••••
French	••••
English	••••

Eduardo Salazar

Full Stack Developer

Profile

Experienced Full Stack Developer working in the accounting industry at the Information Technology Services area in the Innovation Department. Skilled in Spanish, English, French, Teamwork, WISA web solution stack (Windows Server, Internet Information Services, Microsoft SQL Server and ASP.NET), Blazor framework and various development languages. Currently working as a self-motivated Full Stack Developer focused on project execution. Self-directed learning and software development are my passion.

Employment

Analyst Semi-Senior

Sep 2021 - Present

Ostos, Velázquez & Asociados - KPMG, Caracas - Venezuela

- Create new digital products
- Transform, adapt and bringing routines or working methodologies to the digital world
- Applying the Scrum framework on a day to day basis
- Designing and developing Web Applications in an ASP.NET Blazor
- Front-End development with: CSS, HTML5, JavaScript
- Back-End development with: C#
- Services: Claim Transformations, Active Directory
- Using SQL management studio to create relational database for projects
- In charge of Development and Production environment using virtual servers, IIS Manager and database using SQL Server Manager
- Train new annalists in Blazor, relational databases, object-oriented programming and more
- Give support through Service Desk for several internal applications

Consultant 1

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021

Ostos, Velázquez & Asociados - KPMG, Caracas - Venezuela

- Create new digital products
- Propose and develop digital solutions to customer problems
- Transform, adapt and bringing routines or working methodologies to the digital world
- Applying the Scrum framework on a day to day basis
- Designing and developing Web Applications in an ASP.NET (Framework) MVC model
- Designing and developing Web Applications in an ASP.NET Core MVC model
- Front-End development with: CSS, HTML5, JavaScript
- Back-End development with: C#
- Services: Claim Transformations, Active Directory
- Using SQL management studio to create relational database for projects

Mathematics Tutor

Jan 2014 - Aug 2019

Self-employed, Caracas - Venezuela

Multipurpose worker

Sep 2013 - Jun 2016

SARL SBSE- Speed Burger, Saint-Étienne - France

Multipurpose worker

May 2013 - Sep 2013

AVB Services SARL- Domino's Pizza, Lyon - France

Hobbies

- Climbing
- Play Bass Guitar
- Reading
- Learning

Multipurpose worker

AVB Services SARL- Domino's Pizza, Lyon - France

Education

Agile Management with Scrum

Aug 2020

Sybven, Caracas - Venezuela

Computer sciences

Sep 2016 - Aug 2019

May 2012 - Aug 2012

Universidad Central de Venezuela, Caracas - Venezuela

Industrial Design

Sep 2013 - Sep 2014

EDAA, Saint-Étienne - France

Bank, Law and Economy

Sep 2012 - Aug 2013

IFC, Saint-Étienne - France

Civil Engineering & Mechanical

Sep 2010 - Aug 2012

Engineering

Université Claude Bernard (Lyon I), Lyon -

France

Physics, Chemistry Engineering Science

Sep 2008 - Aug 2010

Université Claude Bernard (Lyon I), Lyon -

France

Scientific Baccalauréat Title

Sep 2007 - Jun 2008

Colegion Francia, Caracas - Venezuela